fujitsu-general.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy - FUJITSU GENERAL GLOBAL

Fujitsu General Limited (FGL) is concerned about privacy issues and has prepared this Privacy Policy to make You familiar with how FGL collects, uses and discloses information (including Personal Information (as defined below)) in connection with Your use of the "Services", which consist of (i) FUJITSU GENERAL Website (the "Website"), and (ii) all services and content provided by FGL relating to this Website.

By using this website, You agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If You do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this website, By providing Personal Information (as defined below) to FGL, You acknowledge that such Personal Information may be used and disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy

## 1\. Personal Information Collected From You

"Personal Information" is information that identifies You as an individual or relates to an identifiable person. FGL collects the following Personal Information about You in connection with Your registration for and use of the Services:

  * First and last name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Fax number

## 2\. Other Information Collected From You

"Other Information" is any information that does not reveal Your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual. In addition to Personal Information, FGL also collects (both actively and passively) the Other Information listed below in connection with Your use of the Services. FGL may use Other Information for any purpose, provided that if FGL is required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then FGL may use it for the purposes for which FGL uses and discloses Personal Information as detailed in this Privacy Policy. Other Information that may be collected through Your use of the Services includes:

  * Usage Data: FGL may collect certain usage data and statistics from You, such as when, how, and how much You have used the Services.
  * Device Data: FGL may collect the IP address of Your device using or accessing the Services.

## 3\. Aggregated Personal Information.

Aggregated Personal Information is Personal Information and other information in an aggregated form that does not personally identify You or any other use of the Services. For example, FGL may aggregate Personal Information and/or Other Information to calculate the percentage of users accessed from a specific area. FGL may use and disclose such Aggregated Personal Information for any purpose. For example, FGL may share such Aggregated Personal Information with our affiliated companies, agents and business partners, including for their marketing and other business uses, and/or disclose user statistics in the form of Aggregated Personal Information in order to describe FGL’s Services to current and prospective business partners and to other third parties for lawful purposes.

## 4\. How Your Information is Used 

Without limitation to Section 3, FGL may use Your Personal and Other Information without further notice to You for the following purposes:

  * To provide You with the Services, including to respond to Your inquiries and fulfill Your requests; and
  * For FGL’s internal business purposes, such as data analysis and analytics, developing new products and services, and providing, maintaining, developing and enhancing the Services

## 5\. Sharing Your Personal Information with Third Parties

FGL is not in the business of selling Your information. However, in certain circumstances, FGL may share Your Personal Information with third parties without notice to You, including for the purposes set forth above in Section 4 and/or under the circumstances set forth below and for other lawful purposes:

  * FGL’s Subsidiaries and Affiliated Companies

FGL may share Your Personal Information with FGL’s subsidiaries and affiliated companies. FGL is the party responsible for the management of the jointly-used Personal Information.

  * Authorities and Law Enforcement Agencies

As FGL believes to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside Your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside Your country of residence; (d) to enforce FGL’s terms and conditions; (e) to protect FGL’s operations or those of any of FGL’s affiliated companies; (f) to protect FGL’s rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of FGL’s affiliated companies, You or others; and (g) to allow FGL to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that FGL may sustain.

  * Other Third Parties

To third parties in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition, directly or indirectly, of all or any portion of FGL’s business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

## 6\. Security

FGL seeks to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within FGL’s organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If You have reason to believe that Your interaction with FGL is no longer secure (for example, if You feel that the security of Your account has been compromised), please immediately notify FGL in accordance with the "Contacting FGL" section below.

## 7\. Choices and Access

As outlined in this Privacy Policy, You can always choose not to provide Your Personal Information to FGL through the Services. However, doing so may prevent You from obtaining certain information using certain Services.

  * Receiving electronic communications from FGL

If You no longer want to receive marketing-related emails from us on a going-forward basis, You may opt-out by following the instructions in such emails.

  * FGL’s sharing of Your Personal Information with its affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes 

If You would prefer that FGL not share Your Personal Information on a going-forward basis with FGL’s affiliated companies for their direct marketing purposes, You may opt-out of this sharing by the instructions in the applicable emails. 

If You opt-out of receiving any of the foregoing communications through the methods outlined above, FGL will try to comply with Your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that FGL may still send other messages to You, such as administrative or Services-related messages.

## 8\. Review/Update Your Personal Information

If You wish to access, modify, and/or update the Personal Information You provided to FGL, You may do so by contacting FGL in accordance with the "Contacting FGL" section below.

If You have any questions regarding FGL’s handling of the information You provide to FGL please contact FGL at Our Inquiry Form.

Please make Your request clear. For Your protection, FGL may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that You use to send FGL Your request, and FGL may need to verify Your identity before implementing Your request. FGL will try to comply with Your request as soon as reasonably practicable.

Please note that FGL may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes, and there may also be residual information that will remain within FGL’s databases and other records, which will not be removed.

## 9\. Retention Period

FGL will retain Your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

## 10\. Use of Services by Minors

The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and FGL requests that they not provide Personal Information through the Services. If You are under thirteen (13) please do not provide FGL with any Personal Information. If You have reason to believe that a child under the age of thirteen (13) has provided Personal Information to FGL through the Services, please contact us and FGL will endeavor to delete that information from its databases.

## 11\. Transfer of Personal Information

The Services are controlled and operated by FGL from Japan. Your Personal Information is stored and processed in Japan, and by using the Services You consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of Your country of residence which may have data protection rules that are different from those of Your country. In certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in those other countries may be entitled to access Your Personal Information.

## 12\. Sensitive Information

FGL asks that You not send, disclose or otherwise make available to FGL any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, or criminal background) on or through the Services or otherwise. 

## 13\. Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of code which is sent from our servers to your computer. It does not contain any personal information and is used to improve the functionality of the website and also to anonymously track user visits, to enable us to improve the overall user experience by making improvements to the website. We do not use information based on your location, IP address, internet service provider, company or other identification data. We may, for example, track the overall number of visitors to a specific page, or record where site visitors are coming from and which search terms were used to find us.

For further information on what cookies are, how FGL use them, and for details of how cookies can be disabled, please see our Cookie Policy.

## 14\. Modifications to Privacy Policy

FGL may change, modify, and update this Privacy Policy at any time. The "LAST UPDATED" legend at the top of this page indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Your continued use of the Services after such changes indicates Your acceptance of such changed terms.

## 15\. Contacting FGL

If you have any questions regarding FGL’s handling of the Personal Information You provide to FGL, please contact FGL at Our Inquiry Form.

If you want to contact us by e-mail, because email communications are not always secure, please do not include sensitive information in Your emails to FGL.
